annies-eats.net 2017-06-21

# Privacy Policy - Annie's EatsAnnie's Eats

**Last Updated: 9.21.14**

This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) applies to the information Annie’s Eats, Inc. (“Annie’s Eats,” “we,” “us”) collects about you from any devise you use to access our website located at www.annies-eats.com (the “Site”) and how we use that information. Please note that the Privacy Policy applies solely to our online information-gathering and dissemination practices in connection with the Site and does not apply to any of our practices conducted offline. Your use of the Site, the email subscription service, and our online store (together “Services”) indicates you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and indicates you agreement to abide by the Terms of Service in effect. If you have any questions or comments about the Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at www.annies-eats.com/contact.

 **Information Collection**

We gather “Personal Identifiable Information” (or “PII”), “Site Usage Data,” and “IP Addresses” through the Site. PII is information that identifies a person as an individual such as your name, company, and title, postage address, telephone number, and email address. Site Usage Data is aggregated information, demographic information, and any other information that does not reveal a person’s specific identity. An IP Address is the Internet Protocol address of the computer that you are using.

 _Personally Identifiable Information_

You do not have to provide us with your PII to use this Site. However, we offer an opportunity for users to leave comments on particular articles or posts of interest or subscribe to our daily email subscription service. We may also offer, from time to time, access to our online store. The use of these Services may require you to provide PII. We collect PII from you only when you voluntarily provide it to us.

 _Online Store_

From time to time and at our sole discretion, we may provide users with access or links to our online store hosted by Big Cartel (www.bigcartel.com). Big Cartel, including its service providers, parent entity, and affiliates have access to your PII, Site Usage Data, IP Addresses, and other information or aggregates thereof for Big Cartel to analyze performance of our online store, to make changes to Big Cartel’s services and products, and to provide related services, such as payment processing. By using this Site or any other Services we provide, you recognize that you are providing this information voluntarily and that Big Cartel may collect and use this data in accordance with their respective Terms of Use and Privacy Policies. By using this Site or any other Services we provide, you acknowledge that your rights to any information collected and used by Big Cartel will be governed by the agreements and policies relating to Big Cartel. For additional information concerning Big Cartel’s use of your information, visit www.bigcartel.com/agreement.

 _Comments_

In order to enhance their use of the Site, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles or posts of interest. Commenters may register anonymously; however if we are required by law to disclose commenters’ contact information or if a third party complains that a comment breaches our Terms of Service (e.g. libels them), then, in accordance with our Terms of Service, we will attempt to contact commenters to give them the opportunity to respond to such requests. Please refer to our Terms of Service for more information.

 _Links_

This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information, or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any site or service to which the Services link. The inclusion of a link with the Services does not imply endorsement of the linked site or service by us. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects PII.

 _Mailing Lists_

Annie’s Eats may provide a mailing list in order to provide subscribers with relevant information and regular updates from the Site. In order to sign up to receive regular emails, users must provide PII including a valid email address. Users who sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the Site. We may, from time to time, track user email usage in a continued effort to improve our Services.

 _Site Usage Data_

When you visit and interact with the Site, Annie’s Eats and third parties with whom we have contracted to provide services to Annie’s Eats may collect Site Usage Data. Such non-PII may include your MAC address, your computer type, screen resolution, OS version, or Internet browser. Site Usage Data may also include demographic data, such as your location. To enhance your experience on the Site, Annie’s Eats and our service provider may use ‘cookies’ on the Site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We store a cookie on each user’s machine that contains user specific information. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline cookies or be given a choice of declining or accepting the transfer to your computer of a particular cookie, or cookies, from a particular website. We and our service providers may also use various information aggregators or tracking tools (e.g. pixel tags, action tags, web bugs, .gif tags, Javascript, etc.) in connection with Site pages and email messages in certain formats to, among other things, track the actions of Site users and email recipients, to determine the success of marketing campaigns, to determine the presentation of advertisements, and to compile statistics about Site usage. These tools allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of the Sites, to deliver branded services, and to help determine the effectiveness of promotional or advertising campaigns. When use in email messages in certain formats, these tracking tools can tell the sender whether and when the email has been opened.

 _IP Addresses_

Like most standard website servers, we and third parties with whom we have contracted to provide services may collect log files. Log files include IP Addresses, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to PII. We may use a tracking to that uses log files to analyze user movement.

 **How We May Use and Disclose Your Information**

 _Personally Identifiable Information_

We may use your PII to respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, such as to send you newsletters that you request. We may also use your PII to keep record of your contact information and correspondence and to provide notice of new and/or additional services we may choose to provide. We may also send you important administrative or transactional information regarding the Site.

We may provide options to the Site to permit you to send messages and other communications (e.g. tweets, Facebook posts, emails, etc.) regarding Site-related content to other users through the Site. If you wish to use these features, you may be required to provide us with, and we may use, the other person’s email address or username so that we can facilitate you sending of such message or other communication to that person. Please note that any PII you provide in connection with sending messages or other communications regarding Site-related content to others through the Site, such as your name, username, and email address, will, of course, be disclosed to your friend.

We may also use your PII for our business purposes such as data analysis, audits, and enhancing, improving, or modifying our services. We may also use your PII as we believe is necessary to comply with applicable law, with the legal process, to respond to requests for public and government authorities, to enforce our Terms of Service, to protect our operations, rights, privacy, safety, or property, and to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

We may also provide PII about you to our contractors, agents, and designees (specifically including Big Cartel) to the extent necessary to enable them to provide certain Site-related services (e.g. web hosting, improving Site features and functionality, processing payments, or providing maintenance) on our behalf.

 _Site Usage Data_

Because Site Usage Data does not personally identify you, we may use such information for any purpose. In addition, we reserve the right to share such Site Usage Data, which does not personally identify you, with third parties, for any purpose.

In some instances, we may link or combine Site Usage Data and PII. To the extent any Site Usage Data is linked or combined with PII, such information will be treated as PII as long as it is so linked or combined.

 _Third Party Service Providers_

Your Site Usage Data may be made available to third party service providers (specifically including Big Cartel and the Blogher Network) with whom we contract in order to obtain Site-related services (e.g. web hosting, improving Site features and functionality, providing ancillary services, processing payments, or providing maintenance). By using this Site or any other Services we provide, you recognize that you are providing this Site Usage Data voluntarily and that these third party service providers may collect and use this data in accordance with their respective Terms of Use and Privacy Policies. By using this Site or any other Services we provide, you acknowledge that your rights to Site Usage Data collected and used by these third party service providers will be governed by the agreements and policies relating to these third party service providers. For additional information on the terms of these agreements, visit www.bigcartel.com or www.blogher.com. For information about opting out of Gourmet Ads and ad serving partners please visit[http://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy](http://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy)“.

 **Choices and Access**

If you no longer want to receive emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out of receiving these emails by following the unsubscribe instructions in any such message or by contacting us by email at www.annies-eats.com/contact. We will try to comply with your requests as soon as reasonably practicable.

You may request to review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise modify any of your PII that you have previously provided to us through the Services, or object to the use of processing of such PII by us. You may exercise these rights by contacting us at www.annies-eats.com/contact.

In your request, please make clear what PII you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have your PII that you have provided to us suppressed from our database, or otherwise let us know what limitations you would like to put on our use of your PII that you have provided to us. For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the PII associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for processing purposes, and there may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed. We may also, from time to time, re-contact former users of the Site. Finally, we are not responsible for removing information from the databases of third parties (such as service providers) with whom we have shared PII about you.

 **Additional Information**

 _Security_

We seek to adopt commercially reasonable security measures consistent with other similarly situated business enterprises to assist in protecting you against the loss, misuse, and alteration of PII that is under our control. Unfortunately, no data storage system or system of transmitting data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers, the means by which PII is transmitted between your computer and our services, or any PII provided to us or to any third party through or in connection with the Services. If you believe your connection to our Site is no longer secure, please notify us as soon as possible.

 _Use of the Site by Children_

The Site is not directed to children under the age of thirteen (13), and Annie’s Eats does not knowingly collect PII from children. If you are younger than thirteen (13) years old, please do not provide PII while using the Site.

 _Retention Period_

We will retain PII about you for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law and/or regulations.

 _Jurisdictional Issues_

Annie’s Eats does not represent or warrant that the Site, or any part thereof, is appropriate or available for use in any particular jurisdiction. Those who choose to access the Site do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for complying with all local laws, rules, and regulations. We may limit the Site’s availability, in whole or in part, to any person, geographic area, or jurisdiction we choose, at any time and in our sole discretion. By using the Site and submitting any PII, you consent to the transfer of PII to other countries, such as the United States of America, which may provide a different level of data security than that provided in your country of residence.

 _Contacting Us_

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at www.annies-eats.com/contact. Please note that all communications will not necessarily be secure; accordingly you should not include credit card or other sensitive information in your correspondence with us.
